SUSHAN SHRESTHA

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Technically-oriented and seasoned professional with dedicated years of experience overseeing site operations. Extensive knowledge in beverage industry -hospitality and customer service possessing strong networking, organizational and problem solving skills with an aptitude to excel and grow.

WORK HISTORY

Bartender, 08/2019 to Current Hobart Airport - SSP Australia, Hobart, TAS

- Managed bar inventory, restocked supplies and placed orders for spirits, beer, wines and mixers.
- Upsold menu items to customers, driving up per sale revenues and maximizing profits.
- Kept accurate inventories and notified management of ordering needs for liquor, beer, wine and bar supplies.

Purchasing Assistant, 11/2018 to 07/2019 ACCOR Hotels - Mercure Central, Sydney, NSW

- · Ledger entry and bookkeeping
- Verified receipt of items by comparing items received to items ordered and resolved shipment order errors with suppliers.
- Income and Expenditures Report, Accounts Payable, EOM reporting and data entry.
- Oversaw purchase order shipments by managing deadlines and cancellation dates.
- Established and managed supplier and vendor relationships.

Barman, 01/2017 to 07/2019 Stockade Brewery, Sydney, NSW

- Organized bar inventory and storage procedures to keep stock within optimal levels and meet expected customer demands.
- Maintained secure cash drawers, promptly resolving discrepancies for accuracy.
- Developed new signature cocktails to support bar marketing brand and increase profits.

Site Manager, 04/2013 to 12/2018 Meriton Suites, Sydney, NSW

- Established employee work schedules to properly staff departments for daily shifts.
- Interviewed, hired and trained staffs.
- Ensured projects were completed according to approved time, quality and cost estimates.
- Delegated assignments based on site plans, project needs and knowledge of individual team members.
- Oversaw employee attendance record, handled payroll and ordered new materials for sites.
- Provided general office administration, including correspondence, filing and spreadsheet development.

Address: Sorell, TAS 7172 **Phone**: 0424700755

Email: shresthasusan@yahoo.com

SKILLS

- Responsible alcohol service
- Hospitality service expertise
- Handling difficult customers
- Reporting and documentation
- Performance improvement
- Staff Management
- Engaging personality
- Liquor, beer and wine knowledge
- New hire training
- Proficient in Oracle, Purchase Plus ,MYOB,Guest Centrix and other databases.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Accountancy, Accounting And Finance, 06/2018

KOI Institute - 400 Kent Street, Sydney

Diploma, Leadership And Management, Expected in 08/2020 ALTEC College - Hobart

TESTIMONIALS

- "Sushan was absolutely fantastic in Hobart Airport bar. We had a long wait until our flight. He was friendly, accommodating, funny. Had a great time with him. We weren't the only patrons to comment on him either. He is an asset to you!"- Steph Anstey 09/2019
- This level of professionalism goes above and beyond his role as a manager, He follows through on all his tasks well, and is very quick in his responses and follow-up. He is able to maintain a sense of composure even during urgent matters and this gives me a sense of ease and confidence in working with him" Unique Raj Onta (Area Manager- ECOLAB Australia)